You see that guy with the two Bugattis,
a jet, and a multi-million dollar house?
Yeah, that's me now. But this isn't how
it started. Back then, I was just
another kid showing up to class, working
a 9 to5, living with my parents. I
wasn't special, but I just wanted more.
The same dream that [music] most of you
have right now, to change your life.
See, I didn't come from money. I didn't
win the lottery. And I definitely did
not get lucky. What I did was make a
decision that no matter where I started,
I decided where I would end up. And this
is where it all began.
>> I want the money [music]
in [singing] the cars. Cars in the
clothes.
[music]
I suppose
I just want to be I just want to be
successful.
>> Honestly, it feels weird driving by
here.
I have not been to campus since I
dropped out of college what five five
years ago, six years ago. I mean, I I've
passed by like the outer street in the
Bugatti just one night because I just
happen to be going around this way. But
I don't know. It's kind of weird that
I'm actually going to go back into the
campus. I'm like very superstitious, you
know? I don't like going back to where I
used to be cuz I feel like it holds me
back and it sets me back. But I feel
like it's time to do this video because
this is where it all started. College.
And this is where
And this is where it all started.
MDC, Miami Day College. As you guys can
see right here, this boys is where I
came to college. This shout out to Miami
Day College because this is where I
realized that
I was just not going to be somebody that
was going to have a regular job. I was
not going to be somebody that got a
degree. I wasn't going to be somebody
that was going to be normal. This school
made me realize that. And I remember
coming into college fresh out of high
school because in the eyes of my
parents, in order for you to be somebody
successful, you have to go to college.
If I didn't go to college, my parents
were going to kick me out of the house.
So, right, like literally fresh out of
high school, took the month of summer,
whatever it is, and then I went right
into college, which was right here. And
I remember that I was not used to
actually taking school serious, right?
In high school, I would skip class every
single other day. I would leave school
early because I had a job when I was in
high school. And I would leave school
early to go to my job. And I just pretty
much only had like two classes. I would
leave school after like 3 4 hours, which
is great, right? Cuz I would just go do
whatever I want. But I got used to not
doing anything and just getting by and
pretty much graduating. Like I was
really living life however I wanted.
Like nobody could tell me anything. All
my parents cared about was school. And
as long as they saw a degree, they
didn't care how I got it. as long as
they saw that I graduated high school.
They didn't care how I graduated. And I
took that same energy to here. And boy
was I wrong. Was I hit with a reality
check. Uh none of my friends from high
school came to the same college that I
did. Everybody that was were my friends
that either didn't go to college or they
went to a different college. So I was
kind of the only guy doing this new
thing. I met new people here and it just
really wasn't what I thought it was
going to be. Being the kid that does
whatever you want to high school, being
a problematic kid, you kind of think
you're a rebel and then you pretty much
could do whatever you want. College
isn't really like that, especially when
you actually have to pay to be here or
financial aid. And I don't know, just
like a big reality check for me. And
that's when I had to find like a
different solution to life, right?
Because I just I knew I did not want to
come through college. I did not want to
be somebody that just gets another
degree because at the end of the day,
I'm like, "Okay, I get this degree, then
what?" And I have to go get a job. Like
my goal was to be a cop. Like literally
do this right here. Be a police officer.
And I I love law enforcement and I
believe in them and I I think it's all
great, but I just didn't see myself
working one hour for $25 or $50 or $75
or $100. I just didn't see my time be
valued at something. I saw my knowledge
and what I'm good at be valued at
something. And I just didn't know what
that was at that time or what it could
be. And this is where it all started.
This is literally
where I was forced to make that decision
to be a bigger and better person. It's
not really superstitious, right? Like I
have not like I'm going to open the door
with my pinky.
>> You don't want the germs on I don't want
this energy, bro. Bro, I have not I have
not walked in here since I dropped out.
This is where I spent half of my time
learning how to make money online
because I couldn't be home. I couldn't
be at a job because my parents were
tracking my location and they saw that I
had to be at a college campus in order
for me to still be living at the house.
And the location says that I was at
school. I just wasn't in class because I
was already going to fail anyways and I
couldn't watch videos in class. I
couldn't do anything else other than
just pay attention to the teacher and I
could give a [__] what the teacher was
saying. So I would spend my time here in
the library, have my headphones on. I
was in the one of the corners over there
and I would just basically be figuring
out ways of how to make money online. So
this library
in here, bro, this library saw the
beginning early stages of Alex Gonzalez
learning how to make money online. Like
what is money online? what is a
business? What is everything? It's just
kind of learning something aside from
reading English from what is the square
root of pi of whatever. Like this is
where I started to actually understand
real world things that were going to
lead me to become successful, not just
be another robot to solve solutions. So,
I would sit in one of these cubicles
right here in the library.
Literally right here or right here.
No, no, no. Go ahead. I was already
there a couple years ago. 7 years ago
when I would study in this library, I
would be sitting in one of those
cubicles right there.
Crazy. Not once in my [__] life that
I come in here and say,
"Yep, how to cleanse your body and your
mind." Jeffrey,
>> that sounds like a good book.
>> Yeah. No, I'm not going to lie, Jeffrey.
This looks like a great book for where I
am in now in life. But an 18-year-old
should not be reading this. The
evolution of human sex differences. Yo,
we were monkeys, dude, at one point of
our life. 100%. You don't believe in
that?
>> Probably not.
>> What do you mean, bro? To me, if I would
ever read a book, I need to see
pictures. No pictures.
No read. Why am I touching things, bro?
>> No. Don't Don't put it on me. [laughter]
>> Tell me.
>> You think I want it? Who's going to pay
for the [__] Bugatti? You know, I
came to college here.
>> Oh [__] For real.
>> This is literally where I
>> Which is such a [__] coincidence,
bro.
>> Dude, we literally just came here cuz
we're like eating late from class and
we're like, [music]
>> dude, he was like, "What the [__] are
those guys doing?" [laughter]
>> I'm like, "Wait, that's [__] Alex,
bro."
>> No,
>> guys. Hey, bro. Do you mind if we take a
little picture?
>> Yeah, let's do it.
>> Let's do it, bro.
>> This is [__] crazy, bro.
>> This is crazy.
>> Like, I used to, bro, I walk down these
same halls, bro, and I was like,
>> All right, so we're pulling up right now
to the cafeteria. This is where I would
like when it was like too hot outside
and I didn't want to eat outside or be
outside, I would be here. This how you
know I came to a small college. This is
the cafeteria.
>> That's it.
>> Yeah, this is it. This is the whole
cafeteria. You would have this kind of
little store here that was connected. I
guess they put a glass now or whatever.
But yeah, this is where I would spend my
other 40% of the time and then I spend
10% of of the time on another spot, but
I would just sit anywhere here. The
chairs, everything was displayed very
differently. I guess it was like a
bigger one of these tables. This is like
a couple years ago. It was like 6 years
ago. So I I I just I didn't want anybody
to see my computer, so I would literally
just sit right here and just have my
back to the wall and just be on my
computer like a little It was literally
like right here. I would get hungry, get
up, walk up to the little bakery, get
some food, sit back down, and when my
class was supposed to be over, I
basically would get in my car and leave.
This cafeteria is where I spent 40% of
my time when I wasn't at the library.
Yeah, this is it.
[laughter] All right, so this is the
class where I was sitting. Like, bro,
you going to get goosebumps, bro. I was
literally sitting Well, these are brand
new desks, bro. Cuz they used to not be
like this at I would say right here in
this same not this same exact chair, but
it was this spot. I was second to last
on the second row. Bro, it's crazy how 7
years ago I was in this same exact seat
as a [__] regular kid, bro.
[laughter]
Bro, yeah, you can't make this [__] up,
bro. Look at this. Look, look, look,
look at your boy, bro. She was 100%
knocking out like that, dude. She was
literally right here falling asleep.
Look at this. That is your boy Alex
Gonzalez in college in this same exact
seat right there filming his classmates
fall asleep.
Let me see if I still like
100%.
What is this?
Bro, I'll knock out. You give me 5
seconds. I'll knock out. I would be like
this. I remember it was a Tuesday
morning 7:00 in the morning. This was
the first class that I had when I would
come to college. And I remember I would
just come to class to come to class and
I would just literally be here and I
would just be sitting like this and just
days off, fall asleep or just literally
be looking at the floor or be on your
phone cuz you could be on your phone in
college. And the day that the professor
told me and he came up to me, I remember
he walked right down this aisle right
here. If you walk down this aisle and he
came up to me, he's like, "Hey, look."
He put his hand on my shoulder. He's
like, "Hey, look, Alex, just letting you
know you can pretty much ace every
single test from this point to the end
of this semester and you're still going
to fail this class. Just letting you
know. So, you don't have to come back.
Um, you want to go ahead and renew." He
was very polite about it, but he's
basically said, "You're screwed." And I
looked at him and I'm said, "Sorry, sir.
I'm I'm I'm going to try my best to at
least make up for last time, do some act
curriculum, whatever the [__] I said."
He walked back and then from that point
forward something shifted in my mind
because like this man has literally like
manifested and he he he embedded in me
that I was a failure and I know I'm not
a [__] failure. I know that I'm
capable of doing whatever the [__] I
want and I know I'm capable of being
successful and being the best version of
myself. And that's where the mission
turned on to show that [__] that
I'm not a failure. To show that
[__] that I can do whatever the
[__] I want when I want, how I want. I
just have to figure out what I'm good at
and how I can capitalize that skill. And
I don't regret him telling me that one
bit. I am actually grateful that he came
and told me that because if he would
have never told me that, he would have
just let me fail and then who knows what
would have happened from that point on.
Maybe there would be no Alex Street.
Maybe there would be no FX Alex the best
trader in the industry or the crazy
turning $100 into a million. Who knows?
But I would say that that created the
perfect storm for me to turn into the
new version of myself because I know I'm
not a [__] failure. And ju just
because I'm not good at reading whatever
the professor wants me to read out loud
because of my accent or because I'm not
good at solving a complex math equation,
that doesn't mean I'm not going to
succeed. That just means I'm not good at
doing this textbook [__] But I'm
good at real life situations, real life
money making decisions, real life risk,
not how long did the train get to get to
point B if X, Y, and Z is the square
root of five. Who gives a [__] I don't
know. I just don't understand how
somebody can stand in a [__]
classroom like, bro, I stand right now
in front of auditoriums with thousands
of students. And when I stand in front
of an auditorium with thousands of
students, I want to I want to get the
message across that you could also be
successful. you can also become the best
version of yourself. How the [__] can
somebody some old dude just stand right
here and say you need to understand what
is the square root of five for you to
actually have purpose in life? It's the
wrong message to the people like the
people that are going to change this
world are going to be the new youth, the
new me, the new you guys watching this
video. And you being forced to learn
something that you're never going to use
in a real life situation. I think it's
the biggest waste of time ever and it
gets your mindset turnurning in the
wrong directions. So, I don't know, man.
And I'm talking out there for like the
people that want to I don't know. Let's
say you want to be a a cop like I did.
Why the [__] do I have to be studying
math, dude? Like, why do I have to be
studying English? I don't need to learn
any of these stuff. Like, if you're
going to be a doctor out there, if you
want to be a a first responder, I get
it, right? Like, you guys I I I salute
to you guys. We appreciate your guys'
service. your guys is different and your
guys' purpose is different and that's
what you guys want to do. But to people
that are just getting started into their
journey, I I just don't think giving
them all this unnecessary curriculum,
it's going to lead them to even know
where they want to go. I want to leave a
message to the people that come to this
[__] class tomorrow or whenever the
[__] and they know that they don't have
to be here to become successful. It's
exactly what I'm going to say.
>> You should put a quick signal on there.
>> I am. Yeah. I'm actually in a trade
right now, bro. You know what it is that
I'm up right now? $153,000
on the trade. In one single week, I'm
making $154,000
a week. And the person that was [__]
teaching me here in this class right
here was barely making $50,000 a year.
Why would I ever take advice from
somebody that is making a tenth of what
I make on a week and making it a year?
Makes no [__] sense. You don't have
to be here to be successful.
>> Well, back in the day, legend says it
that the teacher was making more than
you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You don't have to be
so successful.
>> Sus think it's with one L, but I mean
[__]
>> the extra L's.
>> We're always taking extra L's [laughter]
>> by [clears throat] your boy
Alex G. [__] D. Yo, did they
hear the Spanish music?
>> That's how you know you're at a college
in Miami, bro. Spanish music throughout
this whole [__]
That feeling once you became rich and
never went to college.
>> Latinas.
>> Damn thing from for Latinas. Oh,
brother.
You want to solve world hunger? You want
to solve anything in the world? Get you
some [__] Latinas. Just solve
anything.
[music] All right, boys. is and this is
where I would spend the other 10% of my
time. So when people are in class, I was
out here because you the cafeteria was
full, library was full, skipping class.
So I'm just out here. I'm basically
waiting for, you know, 4 hours out of
the day to go by so my parents can see
that I am in college and that I am
supposedly doing something and they
don't keep me out of the house. So I had
nowhere else to go on the campus. It was
a very small campus. So I would just
chill here. I can't remember which
table. I know. I know it was a table
like this one. I would sit down in one
of these tables of the back rest. I
can't tell if it was this one over
there. I'm sure they moved them around
there. It's been a couple years. And I
would just sit here by myself exactly
how this is right now. Like this is a
this is a weekday. Right now it is
Thursday at 3:00. Obviously, I was here
a little bit earlier, but you know,
classes are still going. And I would
just be here by myself because nobody
wants to be outside in the heat. And I
would just watch the classes, just
figure out how to make money online cuz
I had to make money before I supposedly
graduated college, right? I had to
become successful before my two years of
going to college were done because I was
going to break it to my parents. Hey,
just letting you know I do not have a
degree that I graduated college. But
I've been lying to you guys for the last
year and a half, but I've made x amounts
of money doing this, right? That was my
plan. My plan was to just fake go to
college for 2 years until I made it. And
instead of showing them a degree, I was
going to show them a paycheck.
That's not how it went. Show them a
different paycheck for my other job,
Dunkin Donuts. But let's go to my other
job so I can show you guys how that
went. All right, so in here we are
driving into
my old job.
Dunkin Donuts. Yo, that's [__] wild.
You want to know something? Like I've
driven by here again. Like I' i've been
out right out here in the Bugatti and
couple of cars for some videos, but I've
never walked back into the Dunkin Donuts
ever. From the day that I left that job,
I've never walked back in.
It's wild. I used to park my car right
here.
All right. So, I used to work at this
very Dunkin Donuts right here. I
literally have pictures. We'll probably
pop them up right now where I would park
my Infinity. So, I would literally
either go to school really early in the
morning or come to work very early in
the morning. I think I work 3 days out
of the week, 4 days out of the week, and
then I went to school the other days.
So, it was either early morning school
or early morning work or late afternoon
school or late afternoon work. I would
literally park my Infinity right here in
this same exact parking spot. And it was
crazy, right? Because everybody in the
morning needs their donuts and their
coffee in the morning. So, I would have
a line of people line up through this
Dunkin Donuts pretty much like halfway
through this shopping center. And it was
quick. It was me and three other guys
just banging coffees out every single
morning just giving. It was very fast.
And I remember like it got to the point
where I was literally a machine, right?
I wouldn't even have to ask the people
for what they would want because I would
see the familiar faces and I can pretty
much already predict what they're going
to want. If it's a hot coffee, it's
going to be a large with two sugar, one
cream. Like I just remember I would be a
machine and I would look up and that's
it. It was time for me to leave. And
that was cool because it didn't feel
like I was really working. Felt like I
was a machine. But then I realized one
day and I'm like, "Holy [__] I'm just
wasting my time here." Like I am
literally just being a robot just
fulfilling these people's needs and I'm
not getting anything in return. Yeah,
I'm getting my 8 n bucks an hour plus
tip which was terrible and this was back
in the day. Like I know minimum wage has
gone up but I made [__] money working
here. Like it was cool, right? Because I
kind of had to deal with everybody in
this block. So the Wendy's down over
here, right? So if you guys can see the
Wendy's. So that Wendy's, I was boys
with everybody around the clock on that
schedule. And they would come get donuts
or get coffee, get whatever they would
want. And I would get free crispy
chickens. I would give the people at the
Subway free everything. I would get free
foot longs. The bank that I would use is
the bank right here next door. This used
to be a Wells Fargo. That right there
was a Wells Fargo that I used to bank
with. And I would get the money from
Dunkin Donuts and then I would just go
and deposit it right into there. Like
everything was like I controlled or at
least I felt like it. And after working
here for a year, I realized that I
wasn't growing. I was just the same
person. I wasn't making more money. I
was in the exact same spot. And I would
just like look out of this window and
just be like, "Bro, I spend half of my
day in here." And by the time I got out
of here, I'm so tired that I don't want
to do anything else. And I was just
trying to figure out ways how to make
money online. Like I'm super super
superstitious. Like I will never walk
back inside of this store ever again in
my life. Ever. I I'm good. Like I'll
stand outside, sure, but like I would
never go back inside that shopping
center because I did so much work to get
out of that position. I took so much
risk, so much time was lost of me inside
of this place that I don't want to step
back inside the store.
>> So I remember as I was working at Dunkin
Donuts that I would see like a pattern
of people that would come in every
single day, right? You had your people
that would come in and they were the the
7 to2, right? Then there was the 8 to3
and then the 9 to5. 7 to three, 8 to4, 9
to5ers. like it was a different type of
people that worked in these different
hours. And it got to the point where I
would literally see the same exact
people every single morning at the exact
same time. I remember that there would
be a group of people around 11 12:00
that they would come in and they would
ask for their coffee. They would ask for
whatever, but they would hang around and
they would just stay there. They would
have their computers open and what they
would do is work from the Dunkin Donuts,
work from the Subway next door, work
from wherever, right? These people would
literally just be on their computer. And
I remember one day I was going up to I
was just like walking around mopping the
Dunkin Donut store and I'd look over
their shoulder and one of the guys, I
think he has like an Amazon store open
like it looked like he had a business,
right? Cuz he had a website and he had
like a spreadsheet. To me at that
moment, I'm like, this guy had his own
business. And another day, same exact
thing. It was a different guy. He had
like some charts on, so he could have
possibly been a trader. But that let me
realize that there is other ways to make
money. And I don't have to be in this
place to make money. I don't have to be
inside of this facility, inside of this
Dunkin Donuts to make money. I can be
outside of here and still be making
money because these people are probably
waking up at 9 10:00 in the morning. By
the time they get here, it's 11:00 in
the morning. That's when they're
starting their day. I like the idea of
that. I like the idea of starting my day
when I want to. I like the idea of being
able to make money from wherever. And
that's where this this spark ignited in
me to go and figure out a way on how to
make money outside of Dunkin Donuts.
Like this is where it really started to
click for me that and if I really wanted
to scale and I really wanted to grow. I
can't beat here at Dunkin Donuts. I
literally was a robot. Every single
morning I would just get the I I think
the cup was on the right hand side. I
would get it, put it into the sugar
machine, click one button, put it into
the cream machine, click another button,
put the cover on it, hand it to the
person, and repeat that for hours until
I would leave. And I realized after
doing this for hours that I wasn't
growing. I wasn't making more money. I
wasn't learning anything new. I was just
a robot. Literally just whatever the
order said, I was just fulfilling it,
making it happening, and handing it to
the person. I wasn't growing. I wasn't
learning anything new. I was just
literally doing the exact same thing
over and over and over and over and over
again like a [__] idiot. And I would
see these people come in maybe once a
week or sometimes they would come in and
then they would be like in gym wear the
next day that they would come around.
They would hang around then they
wouldn't come back for another 4 days
and they would it's just kind of their
own schedule. They would do whatever you
want. And that is what made me really
want to become a new version of myself
because being stuck in a place to then
potentially make enough money to then go
be stuck back at home didn't really mean
anything to me. So, as I'm feeling like
a robot, I basically said, you know
what? I'm going to hit up one of my good
friends, George. Right? So, you guys
have probably seen George in the channel
in the past, and he's been a really good
friends of mine. He still is a good
friend to this day. And I hit up George,
and we basically me and him are chopping
him back and forth. George is is well
off. He has a familyowned business. He
has a animal clinic, but he never really
wanted to continue the family business
because he just didn't like it at that
time. And uh me and him kind of go back
and forth and we're like, bro, like we
we need to do something that we just
invest our money and give it a little
bit of time and we make money from it,
right? Like that I think that's how the
entrepreneur mindset works. Like our
goal is to invest money into something
and then that money make us more money.
So, him and I created our first venture
and [laughter] we had a great idea and
let's just say it wasn't so great and
I've never really talked about it. And
right now, we're on our way to George
for us to show you exactly what we did
because I think we did five different
ventures as uh as I started off my
journey [music] as trying to make money
outside in Dunkin Donuts.
>> Told him we're pulling up, but I don't
think he knows what we're doing.
Oh,
>> grown a little bit. [laughter]
>> It used to be only that.
>> Yeah, it used to go that door.
What's up, guys?
>> Boom.
>> That right there.
>> No way.
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> that's how you know we're getting
started. So, our first business idea,
you want to tell them what it was?
>> So, it was buy these two dogs, sight
unseen, and another Where was it? Um,
>> Philadelphia.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Our our goal was to get both of
these dogs and breed them. And then when
we breed them, we would sell them. So,
like the babies cuz they were like they
were popping, right? Like were popping
back then. But um
>> Yeah. Didn't work out.
>> Yeah. I think I took care of it for one
night and then you took care of it for
one night
>> and that's it.
>> And then we just got
>> We got fed up like in a day.
>> Yeah.
>> We bought the dogs on this computer
right here.
>> Yeah.
>> I went and I picked them up in the
airport. Remember?
>> You have videos of that?
>> I have. Yeah. Popular videos of me
picking them up and then that was our
first business, right? So, first
business was the dogs. What was the
second thing?
>> Airbnb arbitrage. [laughter]
Yeah, for real.
>> That was that was a fun couple of weeks.
>> Yeah, that was uh we got sold a big
dream cuz cuz like the the idea was
there, right? So, basically the way our
Airbnb arbitrage works is you go to a a
renter, right?
>> You go to a homeowner and you ask
permission to Airbnb the house.
>> That's basically what we're trying to
do.
>> We How many cold people did we call? We
called.
>> We had a big list. We had a huge map of
areas where we could do it, where we
couldn't [music] do it.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. It was
>> Yeah, that was fun until it wasn't.
[laughter]
We went to one property. We're going to
go to the property now. Remember the one
we went with that with that blonde real
estate girl? Remember?
>> Yeah. That she hid the the roof of your
car.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Because like we pulled up this realtor,
poor realtor. She has like no car. I
guess she was like thugging it out or
something. [music] I'm like, "Yo, I got
you. Like we'll take you to the next
spot."
>> We hit a bump.
>> Ninity [laughter]
at the time, you know. So was
>> But yeah, the drive was always it
though. [music] Yeah.
>> We was trying to do something.
>> Yeah. Yeah, the Airbnb never really
worked out because well, the house that
we were actually looking at to do the
arbitrage, [music] it was old as [__]
>> It was made when in 1920
>> Yeah, it was old.
>> Like 1926.
>> Yeah.
>> But it was the only house in that area
that you could actually do rental like
arbitrage cuz they did the the
short-term rentals.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Uh so right now we're going
to go to the house that we were
literally this close. Remember how we
were like we're going to sign the lease
on that house?
>> I remember the house,
>> bro. It was the old house that has like
the crown in the [music] front. That was
the the the realtor we took.
>> Yeah, that one. Yeah, it was in the
hood. Remember, like on the border of
whatever [music]
>> you remember that I'm just going to pick
around.
>> Yeah, I remember because I went straight
down the block and then it was [music]
like that modern building. I know if I
go you remember
>> and I have pictures.
>> I know it has an alley behind it,
>> bro. I have pictures walking straight
>> like the California houses that they
have like a little alley.
>> Mhm. Mhm.
>> Bro, it's crazy how quick I found it.
That was the house, [laughter]
>> bro.
>> Now looking at it, I don't think I would
pay to stay there as an Airbnb person.
>> No, bro. But this is the only one that
was available.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Look. [music]
>> Who's that [__] right there?
>> I have a video, too. Yeah. Like
>> where is the Look, look at the dates
where you can't even fake this, bro.
[music]
>> 2019.
>> 2019, bro. Trying to So, like this was
this right here. So, I I took
>> We got a contract and remember we paid
to
>> Yeah, we paid an attorney for some
contract like that. That was the Look at
your boy right there [music] sneaking
out of work, bro. That was a realtor
who almost took her home with that [__]
[laughter]
>> You used to be a little mechanic.
>> I tried. I tried. I mean, you were like
I I would, for example, I used to get
like these dirt bikes and these
motorcycles and what I would do is buy
them blown up and me try and fix it and
then sell it. I could never fix it. So,
he would come and fix it.
>> He would fix them. He would ride them
and then they'll break again.
>> Yeah. And then we would sell them just
like that. And then the next that would
suck for the next guy.
>> The car is too. You remember the the
Mitsubishi? The Mirage?
>> The Mirage. That was a piece of [__]
That was [laughter]
But I bought it [__] up. I got it to
run. Oh, he got it to run. And we sold
it to the guy. The guy calls the next
day. Yo, it stopped running. I'm like,
"Brother, what's your problem now,
brother? Has nothing to do with me,
bro?" And
>> what else? The Raptor. The with the
>> the Raptor. I had an ATV. A Raptor 7
700.
>> I remember. Yeah. 00
>> with a Jixir 1000 engine in it. So, it's
like a street bike engine on an ATV. I
had the TRX 400.
>> Yeah.
>> With the Jixir 750 in it.
>> He loves all those
>> weird projects.
>> Yeah. Anything that's like not normal is
my [__]
>> And I don't know, paid out good.
>> We're going to go to the Airbnb, sir.
>> No, I don't really.
>> Thank you very much.
>> We'll uh FaceTime you from the property.
[laughter]
>> All right. So, after I don't know how
many years, [snorts]
we're back. Yo. Yo, it looks so much
better since the last time I was here.
Oh my god. So, this is the house that I
attempted to rent on Airbnb. That's
exactly how it looked like before. Look
at it now. All right. So, as you guys
can see, this is how the house looked
like before. Seems like they remodeled
it and made it look nice. So, our goal
with the Airbnb arbitrage, like the
narrative was perfect, right? We would
basically tell the landlord, it's like,
hey, look, would you want to rent your
property? Because he was just renting
this. I think it was for like 7K a month
or something. And then we would tell
him, "Hey, look, would you want to rent
us the property? 7K a month. We sign a
one-year lease and we just live on the
property. And we're not forced to
maintain the property. We're not forced
to remodel it. We're not forced to
basically keep it to the best condition
that we have to because we can live in
here however we want. Or what if I told
you that every single week I'm going to
make sure this property is on A+ shape.
I'm going to make sure that not only is
it maintained, but that I remodeled it
because my goal is to rent it out to new
people to come in every single week so
that they can actually have a great
experience. They leave a great review
and that means I make more money. So
like the narrative was cool to present
to a landlord, right? like me like I'm a
landlord for a couple of my properties
and like if somebody would tell me that
it would make sense but that we got an
attorney. He drafted up the contract but
then George and I started doing some
math on like all right like you saw how
bad this house was before for us to make
it look half of what it was. So like
decently good enough for it to even get
rented on Airbnb and get good ratings.
It was going to be a lot more money than
we originally had thought to come out of
pocket. So yeah, we never did it. But
yeah, imagine, bro, like
would have been a cool start. But yeah,
we sadly did not do any Airbnb rent to
arbitrage. But this very, very same
house is what then led me to understand,
okay, I can't do real estate. I got to
do the next thing. Let's go on to the
next thing. All right, boys. And this
right here is where it officially
started. This right here where I am
standing right now is where I had my
first transaction with an IML marketer.
How's it going, man? Yeah, I'm here to
I'm here to learn trading. Yeah, man.
Just just come on in. We're going to
show you everything about trading and to
meet other very cool and successful
entrepreneurs. You're going to be around
the right people.
All right. You know, I just left Dunkin
Donuts. I'm 19 years old, 20 years old.
I need this. All right. Let's go.
from here proceed to go inside of this
auditorium and then I get like my first
orientation in the first uh IML right so
it's IM markets live I think it's IM now
it's basically like a multi-level
marketing
business where they use trading as the
driving force to market their
multi-level marketing and they never
taught me anything about trading but
they just put me on onto what trading is
as a whole and this exact same spot is
where all that began and I came to like
five of these different auditorium
meetings and speeches and it's all the
same thing. They're always just selling
you on what trading is but not on how it
works. Like the opportunity that is
inside of trading, it's all great. It's
all fantastic, but make sure you bring
your friend tomorrow to the next uh
ceremony that we're going to be doing so
we can get them on board and they get
involved in trading and then they come
the next time and the next time and they
never teach you trading. It's just the
same thing they repeat over and over
again. But it did put me on to what
trading currencies is. And then this is
like where it all began on for me to
actually learn how trading works. So,
let me actually show you guys what it
looks like.
>> What's up? What's going on?
>> You're real.
>> You are real.
>> Of course, I'm real, bro. Yeah.
>> Hey, what's up, man?
>> How's it going?
>> You look good, bro.
>> I don't know. I don't know who you're,
but you look good. I don't know.
>> It's always on my IG, bro. It's always
on my little bit of everything.
>> But like what you doing right now?
>> Trade. So I like I um when I actually
got started in trading, I got started
like I got recruited here to like the
IML stuff. Yeah, they did like the
events.
>> You I mean you you had Bugatti.
>> No. No.
>> You look expensive. You look like
expensive guy.
[laughter]
>> No, he's poor actually.
>> He's poor.
>> Yeah, he's poor.
>> I don't There might be like a class
going on or some [__] Oh yeah, this is
it. This is literally where they would
host the events at night cuz it would be
open like this. They would just walk in
here and call this [__] themselves. Just
be like, "Yeah, this is my class. I'm
[__] taking something." And this
right here would be full. I'm talking
about full of people learning on the
opportunity that trading is, but they
never actually teach trading. So, this
is the first orientation thing that I
went to. Let me show you the other spot
where I actually have videos of me at
No, bro. I've been on that on that
trading [__] I'm like, "Oh my god, I'm
coming out of here. I'm like I like bro
just how in the morning, bro." Hey, bro.
But no, I like I like watching you, bro.
You're you're an inspiration for sure.
>> Sure, bro. Appreciate it, man.
>> All right, bro.
>> All right. Good seeing you.
>> Got it, bro.
>> So, those doors over there are where all
of the big big big events would be
hosted because you could sit up to like
350 people in there, I think it is or
something. And we're going to try and
walk in now. There's not a class. But
this is where I had a full circle moment
because what was it like about a year
and a half ago after like I've already
been like very successful in trading,
right?
>> Probably like two years and a half,
>> maybe like two and a half years ago. I
was very successful in trading. I grew a
big community and I decided to, you know
what? I want to help people and teach
people in person completely for free. So
I said, "You know what? This day at this
time, I'm going to be inside this
auditorium. I'm going to be teaching
people my strategy completely for free.
Just pull up." That day, I think there
was more than 2,000 people that pulled
up that day for me to just teach them
trading. We had a line that was formed
here and ended all the way. I'm talking
about like at the next school pretty
much. And we basically got kicked out.
There was like a safety hazard. Too many
people. Like nobody fit. And you know
what it is that going from being a
student inside of this class for
something that I knew absolutely nothing
about to then fast forward 4 years later
which is about 2 years ago and I'm
literally teaching people the same skill
set that actually works. I don't know. I
just had like a like a full circle
moment. But yeah, this is where it all
began. So the way I came across trading
was in the other school that I showed
you guys, Miami Day College. I was at
that outdoor cafeteria sitting down
there studying [music] and one of my
friends came up to me and was like,
"Hey, do you have any time to come to
one of these trading events? They're
going to teach us trading." And I was
like, "You know what? [__] it. Why not?
Let's do it." And then that's where we
actually met here with him and met this
other guru that was going to teach me
trading, but he was just some IML guy.
And [music] that opened the doors to
pretty much everything. So having a
friend just come up to me and be like,
"Hey, I've been seeing you like you want
to learn how to do something else." And
that opened up the doors for me to come
here and understand this whole new
world. So basically you could walk into
the class. There's a full-blown class in
there. And so I think I spent about 3
months coming here meeting as many
people as I can meet and realizing that
these networking events weren't going to
teach me anything. So I spent three
whole months essentially wasted. But it
led me to understand that this
multi-level marketing way is not the
way. In order for me to actually become
a profitable trader and understand the
strategy, I need to learn trading. So, I
had to leave this school and we're going
to go now to my mom's house, my parents
house. And I'm going to show you where I
actually sat down and learned trading
where I would be locked in a little
closet in my mom's house for hours. I'm
talking about 9 10 11 hours out of the
day that I could be in there when I'm
not working or going to school where I
actually learned trading. And it got me
to the point where I was able to finally
make my first profit, move out, and so
on and so forth. So, yeah. So, basically
down there is where they would host
these massive [music] webinars. I was
inside of this class probably three
times a week. Like that was how
passionate I was to learn what trading
is and how it works. And every single
time I thought that I would learn
something new, that there's new way of
trading. But at I'm talking about at no
point did they ever teach me trading
like at all. Like imagine sitting in
this and just hearing the same thing
over and over again and you're not
learning anything new. They're just
selling on the new people that you're
bringing. And if you don't bring people,
they almost get mad at you. And it took
me quite some time to realize that, but
that realization led me to finally go do
this on my own.
>> It's just crazy to be here. I don't want
to interrupt the class. I'm going to be
a gentleman, but I am a savage.
[laughter]
I'm a
>> [__] boy, bro.
>> Oh my god. Yo, I always see this
[__] flying down Tendo, bro.
>> Who am I? I'm just a guy. I worked at
Dunkin Donuts and yet there was a
different way to life and I'm just a guy
that didn't [__] give up. That's who
the [__] I am. And that's what I want
you to know me as. Somebody that will
never take no for an answer, somebody
that will never [__] fail, and
somebody that's going to show up every
single day no matter [__] what.
That's who I am. So, FIU, which is the
Florida International University, is
where it pretty much all got started and
I was introduced to what trading
currency is and the very basics of it.
But, you know, I was really only there
for like 2, three months out of my whole
entire journey realizing that I was not
going to learn how to actually have a
profitable strategy with these people.
So, right now we're in my old
neighborhood where I used to live at my
parents house. And this is where I
literally spent tens of hours inside of
a room locked in. It was just my mom's
closet. We're going to go to it right
now, which they turned it into like a
laundry or something. It's been years,
but this is where I literally learned
trading for real. This is where I locked
myself in a room. This is where I blew
30 different profit accounts. This is
where I blew $28,000 of my own and my
parents' money. This is where I myself
never saw light at the end of the
tunnel. This is where I was just with my
head down working cuz I had no other
choice. This is my mom's house and where
I spent a lot of my time in. All right,
so this is my mom's house. So this is
where I spent 10 years of my life. So I
was born in a different neighborhood in
Miami and then I was I grew up in this
house right here for the majority of my
life. I went to middle school in this
house, high school, and then basically
the two of the darkest years of my
journey were
inside of that room right there with the
laundry.
>> Yeah. So, this Yeah. And I I I refuse to
step in here. I've [music] come to my
mom's house here 100 times for whenever
I come see her. I don't come inside of
this room. Not happening. I spent so
much of my time and this used to be like
a very small closet. There used to be
like a window over there that I could
like see outside [music] and they turned
it now into like this closet thing or
whatever. But yeah, I I spent hundreds
of hours inside of here. I [music] never
thought I would see the light of day. I
never thought I was going to become
profitable because like this is was my
office. This is my [music] parents room.
This used to be my room. Now it's turned
into like a little bit of a storage kind
of thing. I'm sure these are probably
like baby pictures of me, but we're not
going to get into that right now. But
let me tell you something. This room has
seen a lot of [__] This might be a
small room. Like this might not seem
like a big move, but bro, I made I made
the most out of this [__] bro. This
where I took a a lot of different types
of trades. Type of trades that I took in
this room and the amount of trades that
have been executed in this room and the
amount of times that window has been
used.
Should be studying on a [__] book.
But I used to be from my room. I would
walk over here and straight into the
office. And the problem was that my
parents would see me in there every
single day because they would literally
have to walk by there to get to the
room. And since I am inside of here all
day every single day, they're like
concerned if like what I'm doing is
actually working or if it's not working.
And you know, when you do something for
2 years and you have no results, you
pretty much think that you're wasting
your time. And I just kept lying to
them, lying to them. Like every single
day, I would be up before they were at
6:00 in the morning. I was already in
there. I would be there before they
would go to sleep at 2:30 in the
morning. Like I was just always in this
room figuring out trading, just looking
at the charts and trying to make it make
sense. And it got to the point where it
made sense and everything clicked. This
pool table has been here
for as long as I can remember. That's
why I'm pretty good at pool cuz I've
always had them at my parents house. But
yeah, I don't know. That room right
there has uh seen a lot of my nights and
early mornings. So, inside of that room
there, I remember losing about [music]
50 different platform accounts. You
know, I would buy 25K challenges, 50K
challenges, 100K challenges, 200k
challenges, blowing them in a week. I
remember depositing 500 bucks, 700
bucks, 500, 300 bucks, blowing it,
blowing it, blowing it, blowing it. And
it just turned into like this dark, dark
[music] journey where it was just me. It
was literally me. My parents would be
here watching TV or they would be in the
little barbecue area that we have over
there and I'm just in there and they
would not have any [__] idea what I
was doing. I would just tell them,
"Trust me, this shit's going to work
out. Trust me, this shit's going to work
out." And I just didn't really know it
was going to work out. I didn't know
when, but I knew if I stayed at
something long enough that it was going
to work. And after 2 years of failing in
the markets and just losing account
after account after blowing account
after account, I finally stopped losing.
And it was such a weird feeling cuz
imagine you're getting into a fight with
somebody or you're you're going to go
become a boxer. And for two whole years,
you're just getting punched in the face
over and over and over and over again.
And this is because you don't know how
to dodge the punches. You don't know how
to how to keep your distance. And after
two years, you stop getting punched in
the face, right? So, every single day
for the last 2 years, you've been
getting punched in the face. When you go
a whole month without getting punched in
the face, you feel very [__] weird.
You almost feel like something's wrong.
Well, that's exactly what happened to
me. I was two whole entire years losing
day after day after day, but I was
learning something every single day. And
then for a whole month, I did not lose,
but I did not make anything. I was just
kind of break even. Then the following
month, I was around break even as well.
And then on the third and fourth month,
I actually started to make a little bit
of profit. And then in that same [__]
room right there, like literally in this
[__] like people don't understand
this [__] It's weird for me to explain
this, but inside of this closet right
here, my mom's closet is where I made my
first $300 in profit in this very room
right here. And the first thing that I
ever bought was a pair of Vans. Those
pairs of Vans I still have to this day.
I wore them one time and I've never worn
them ever again. I'm like superstitious
about wearing. You know why? Because my
first 300 bucks that I made in profit, I
withdrew them. I then bought these pairs
of Vans. I wore them. And guess what
happened to the next day? I blew the
account. So technically, I didn't make
[__] anything. But it did feel like I
accomplished something. So I'm like, you
know what? I'm not going to celebrate so
early. So I can then fall into the same
exact pattern that I just did right now.
But after my first $300 in profit, I
blew it. I went back in the following
month in this [__] room. I made
$28,000. I had a 100K account. I think I
made 30 something% 20some% I can't
remember and I got a 7030 profit split.
I made $28,000 in this [__] room.
From that point forward, my life
changed. I walk through this house like
if I [__] own this [__] when they
were playing pool cuz I would be in
there studying. My dad would be here
playing pool. We come with his friends
drinking beer and like I would have to
close the door, put a shirt under so
like the noise wouldn't distract me cuz
his balls just banging everywhere. And
from that point forward, I said, "From
now on, you guys only play pool when I
say." And then things started to change
a little bit in here, right? From that
day forward that I made those $28,000,
everything completely changed because
the month after that, I made I think an
extra like 12 $15,000. The month after
that, I made like 40k. So in the span of
3 months, I went from losing two whole
years and then about 6 months break even
and then another 6 months where I made
six figures. In those 6 months where I
made those six figures, my life changed
completely cuz I personally thought that
I was going to lose it all. I never
thought that I was going to maintain it.
But it got to the point where it took me
so long to actually get everything that
I had at that point that I felt so
confident and then I made the the bold
decision. I was living in here in my
parents house and outside in the
driveway I had an Audi R8 sitting
outside the driveway and half a million
dollars in the bank account. And a lot
of my friends from high school were
making fun of me because, you know, I
have some neighbors that are friends and
like, you know, they're like they they
they saw the journey and they're like,
"Bro, dude, like why are you still
living at your parents house? You have
all this money. Go move out." Like,
"Brother, I don't think you understand.
I move out of my [__] house. Like,
it's forever. Like, I could never come
back." And I needed to make sure the
money that I was making was going to be
forever. Just wasn't going to be
short-lived or was going to be something
quick. That's a problem with a lot of
people nowadays, bro. They they get
money quick and they just spend it
trying to live this certain lifestyle
because you're seeing it on social
media. Like it's normal to be 18 years
old with a Lamborghini or normal to be
straight out of high school and have a
Ferrari. Like bro, that [__] is not
normal. Like I did not become anywhere
near successful until I was 3 years in
my craft and I was about 21. I became a
millionaire at around 21 22 years old
and I was still not confident to go out
and live by myself and and buy certain
things. Like I bought an Audi R8 because
it puts $20,000 down, $30,000 down, and
I was my monthly payment was [__]
It was like $3 $4,000. Like I'm making
like 20 $30,000 a month. It's a very
small percentage of my income at that
time. And when I decided to finally move
out is when everything completely
changed. I went from being a successful
trader to just a completely different
person. Like my my habits changed. I had
more responsibilities. I actually had
bills that were going to be due every
single month. No matter what, like if I
left a cup of water right here and I
would leave the next day, it would still
be there. That that [__] like shocked me
cuz here in my house, you know, five
people lived in this house. You you
would leave something here like these
bananas would have probably been gone
tomorrow. Like somebody was going to eat
them or something. So, I don't know. But
this is where basically all started for
me, honestly. My my mom's house. And
yeah, I I refused to walk in that
[__] And I I didn't grow up poor.
Like, I grew up in a very nice
household. Like, look at this. This is a
I mean I think this is a very nice house
for what I grew up in. Like we have a
pretty nice pool, a barbecue area over
there. Like I see people online that
some people claim that they grew up or
that they were raised with literally
nothing. Like I'm talking about straight
out the mud and then they got to the
point where they are right now. I can't
relate to that cuz I did not grow up
like that. I grew up in a very healthy
household, very average income. This
probably worth like 5 600k right now,
maybe 700K. And I didn't grow up wealthy
where I got something handed out to me
or I got a check to go do something. Not
at all. I I grew up in a very normal
household. At no point was I starving.
At no point did I need nothing. But what
I was starving and what I did need is
for me to be the best version of myself.
And I think that that is like I can't
relate to people that started from the
mud and I can't relate to people that
got things handed out to them. I can
relate to people that no matter what
[__] position they're in or anywhere
that they are in the world or their
current situation that they want to be
the best version of myself. And that's
what led me to the person to the person
that I am today. Like bro, I didn't like
dude this is not Bugatti rich. I had two
Bugattis. I own a [__] plane, you
know? Like we did not grow up rich or
anywhere near that type of wealth. But I
definitely knew growing up here that
this is not the worst and it's
definitely not the best and I wanted to
go for the best. So
yeah, it's just still weird to me that
we're recording in my mom's house. But
yeah, as soon as I became [__] rich
in here, guess what I did? I [__]
moved out to my first ever apartment,
little penthouse in Dorado. Let's go
show you guys where I [music] went from
being Alex Gonzalez. This is where Alex
Gonzalez was raised, born and raised to
where the famous Alex G was born. So,
let's go. All right, ladies and
gentlemen, we have just pulled up to my
old hood when I officially made it
became [laughter] a millionaire. This is
the building [screaming]
where I became a millionaire. This is
where I went from making I don't know
like 20 30k a month to when I started
making 100 120k a month. This is the
building. That's all right. Let's get
out. Get out. I almost ripped off the
door.
>> So, in 2021,
bro, none of these houses were here.
Like, all this was just grass. I
remember I lived on the last floor of
the penthouse. That was the version of
the penthouse on that column right there
where those chairs are all the way up
there. I had basically both of those
balconies. This was the first building
that I lived in. I think it it was u I
don't I think I was maybe paying like 7
8,000 a month. Two-bedroom apartment and
two bathrooms. It was all I needed at
the time. But this is where I went from
becoming like minor responsibility
straight out of high school, still
living with my parents to officially
living by myself. This is where I went
from not only learning from the mistakes
that I was doing in trading, but to
actually like forcing myself to learn
from those mistakes. Because when I'm
living with my parents, I have minor
expenses. I don't really have to learn
and be the best version of myself.
getting out of my comfort zone, getting
out of my parents house where I would
live here by myself. It's where like
[__] really scuffed me. Yo, I had, you
know, I owned the goat, so I had a goat
living in this apartment. I don't know
if you know, but I would like walk it
through this sidewalk right here.
There's like a there's a dog park over
there and I would walk my goat in the
dog park, bro. People would look at me
like like trust me, it's very friendly.
Just let it be.
[laughter]
>> I'm not going to lie, I need to do your
voice with you. I'm nice to meet you.
>> How's it going? How you doing? How's it
going?
>> This is my girlfriend's dad, by the way.
>> All right, so like like I was saying,
one day I was literally walking through
here in the morning. I forgot what I was
doing. I think I was going to the gym.
There's a gym down the street. And as
I'm walking through out here, I'm like,
"Bro, let me just look up." And when I
look up, my my door, my sliding door is
cracked open. Like, bro, what the [__]
And then when I look again, my goat is
on the balcony peeking through like
those little pillars. And that's when I
realized, holy [__] I have a [__]
living responsibility. Like I remember
another day that I like I literally had
to go back upstairs and put it inside. I
remember I wanted to eat a sandwich. I
didn't have a toaster. I wanted to I
think I wanted to make coffee for like
guests that came over. I didn't have a
coffee maker. Like there's an abundance
of like these small responsibilities and
these small things that I wanted to do
and I just didn't have because my whole
entire life I lived in my parents house.
Like everything was kind of just set up
and it was good. And I was forced to get
out of my comfort zone when I came to
live here. Like you guys can't even
imagine. There was so many other things
that I didn't know were a thing. I was
like 2 days without water because I had
to pay my water, bro. I didn't know how
to pay my water bill, my light bill. It
was an abundance of responsibilities
that I had to figure out and do it on my
own because I wasn't going to go call my
dad to figure that [__] out. He was,
"Brother, you got to go figure it out."
So getting out of my comfort zone made
me the person I am today. And now I'm
obsessed with challenging myself and
constantly getting out of my comfort
zone to become a better version of
myself. I remember living here by
myself, right? So I was here 21 22 years
old and there's like a club down the
street from here, uh, famous booby trap.
And I think I would be there every other
night. I'd get home banged up, drunk. I
would literally just It was just I I was
just trying to live like that lavish
lifestyle that every 18, 20, 21 year old
would want to live as soon as it started
touching money. And I saw my income
coming down. And I saw my focus going
down, my trades coming down, like
everything was just heading downhill cuz
I was living the life. I was having fun,
but I wasn't like learning. I wasn't
growing, I wasn't forcing. And like what
really changed the game for me and where
I really decided to lock in is when I
opened up a free community. So I would
teach people how to trade for free. Like
I would literally just live trade, teach
people. And I would have to stop going
out because I would either wake up late
and miss some trades or I would just be
hung over and I wouldn't want to live
trade in front of people. So I stopped
going out. I'm like, you know what? I
have people that I I I like are asking
me to help them and like it feels good
to help people out. So I stopped going
out and I stopped, you know, getting
drunk and doing, you know, smoking weed,
doing all this stuff because like I
literally had a community of people that
were depending on me and that forced me
to lock in. That forced me to just
become a better version of myself to set
an example for other people. And that's
why I did this in in this building right
here.
I don't know if that's an old neighbor
that leveled up, but shout out to that
guy. But yeah, I I don't know. It's kind
of cool. This building definitely
saw the most amount of growth like
percentage- wise like from the person
that I came into here to [snorts] the
person that I left this building. This
building was actually the first building
where I bought technically my first
supercar cuz according to some people
the Audi R8 is not a supercar. This some
car enthusiast. So I bought my actual
first supercar here. I had my first
McLaren 570S and I had my first
Lamborghini Huracan in this building.
Right. What other car did I had? Oh, and
I had a
>> ghost.
>> An old Rolls-Royce Ghost, but yeah, it
was a 2020 20110 Rolls-Royce Ghost. I
think I paid like 120 grand or some
[__] So, you see where the balcony is?
The window next to the balcony. That was
my office. And I remember just sitting
down there and you you can pop up all
these clips of me walking to go me
sitting in the office. I literally
remember having my monitor be in front
of that window and I would just
literally see it go from daytime to
afternoon to the night time and I'm just
there locked in front of my computer.
Like when I started really doubling down
on that and just doing that over the
course I was here almost for like a year
and a half almost 2 years when I did
that for 6 months consistently like my
income my my trading everything did 180°
turn because just locking it ah bro it's
just I can't even explain the importance
and people always ask what happened to
the goat because just one day I stopped
posting the goat completely. Yeah, that
poor thing splatted. So I I I left it
outside one day and I forgot to put the
little railing around it and it just
jumped out and it landed right down
there and it [__] died. That [__] was
bad, bro. Totally kidding. [laughter]
It almost did though. One day I I left
the balcony door open again. I just
forget. And he was just poking half of
his body out through the balcony just
looking like this. So he was just like
standing halfway through the balcony out
like if that [__] would have
just done this one time, done. Done
deal. After that, I decided to just give
him away cuz, you know, it was a it was
just a mission. Fast forward now, I have
a dog, a cat, 25 chickens, horse, and
all that running around, all that
storytelling leads us to where I am
right now. Pretty much summing
everything up to my home. This is where
I live right now. So, you guys saw where
I first moved out at, where I became a
millionaire. You guys saw my parents
house, and now I live here on this $4
million house. I have my own basketball
court, my own gym, sauna, outdoor
office. have my sevenbedroom house over
here. Kind of crazy how like like I I
grew up well, right? Like I did not grow
up bad, but how I just took it to the
next level. And you know, I've achieved
so much [__] in this journey of me
becoming an entrepreneur, a trader,
whatever you want to call it. Like I've
done so much [__] that I forget. And if
it wasn't for some of like my videos, if
it wasn't for content that I do, I would
literally forget. I forget sometimes
that I streak the Super Bowl. I forget
sometimes that I own two Bugattis, but
technically not really cuz I've still
owned one even though it's been crashed
for like six months. I forgot I own a
jet. Like, we do so much [__] and it's
become so normal in the last couple of
months because we're always striving to
just be the best version of ourselves
that we're just enjoying the journey.
Like, we're having so much fun living
life and just living in the moment that
sometimes we forget even like what all
of this was meant for.
>> You gave away a Lambo.
>> You remember that? I gave away a Lambo.
>> Yo, [laughter] that's right. I gave away
I got I've been robbed like four times.
Um, what else?
>> Went to the FLLA with Steve.
>> Went to the FLLA with Steve. That one I
do remember cuz bro, we [__] almost
died.
>> Uh, we did two meet and greets in
Madrid.
>> We did do that.
>> Did a meet and greet in Africa.
>> Did I I know that. What else did I do?
>> We did two meet and greets in London
also.
>> Oh, in London. Yeah. Did in Colombia. A
lot of things I forgot what happened in
Columbia. We never talk about that. But
>> Oh, bro. I helped this random stranger
turn $1,000 into $100,000. David, I just
>> like the other day.
>> Yeah, but I forgot about that. I just
remember cuz of the screen. So, he broke
the screen. The whole point of this
video of you guys understanding my story
so you guys understand where I was when
I started and how I started just as a
regular person. how I stumbled across
trading, which was almost on accident
because I was just trying to figure out
ways how to make money online. And when
I stumbled across, it wasn't entirely
true. Like I was not being taught
truthfully the information to become a
successful trader. And I figured out
that's what I wanted [music] to do. And
I just decided to just stick to it. I
decided, you know what? I'm going to
make something out of this. I was too
deeply involved that I really had no
other [music] choice. like after losing
for two almost two whole entire years, I
wasn't going to go start from scratch
and go do something else. So, I was just
committed to the game. I ended up
falling in love with the game and it
didn't feel like work anymore. It just
felt like another day in my life. Like I
I always knew I was going to be big. I
always knew I was going to be
successful. I always knew I was not
meant to be a regular person. But I
didn't know this [__] fast I was
going to become so [__] rich. And all
I can say is that coming from Dunkin
Donuts, coming from a regular household,
coming from a happy family, normal
family, if I can do it, so can you. And
I didn't have any cheat code. I didn't
have any shortcut. I didn't have any
hack. The only thing that I had was a
mindset that was never going to let me
down and was going to prove other people
that didn't believe in me who I was in
the best version of myself.
And you do that for long enough and you
show up for long enough and you end up
in a position where the [__] I am now.
You guys seeing this video right now, I
just kind of walked you guys through my
whole entire journey. You guys didn't
really understand. Like I I was 2 months
where I didn't leave my apartment. I was
just locked in there. I would just Uber
eats all my food. I was in there by
myself just trying to figure [__] out,
how to scale, how to build a community.
I was doing everything by myself. Now I
I'm kind of just showing you the
highlights of everything and just
putting to the side all the dark times
and all those dark journeys and those
dark moments. Like I'm not saying that
that's not going to happen to you or
those are inevitable. Those are part of
the game and those are what make
everything worth it. And those are the
moments that actually lead you to
understand what you have to do to
succeed. And I remember making my first
$100,000 trading. I remember making my
first million dollars trading. And when
I would get to that point, it would
never feel like enough. And it's not
because I'm I'm not content, right? Like
I'm very happy with my life. I'm very
happy with what I've achieved and who I
am and what I've done. But there's just
so much more out there to life that if
I'm able to do it and as soon as I get
it done, I look back at who I was and
I'm like, "Bro, I was just a regular
[__] kid working at Dunkin Donuts.
Now I'm making millions of dollars on
the internet this fast." And that just
literally opens up my mindset. If I can
do one, I can do two, I could do three,
I can do five million. And that is my
message that I want to send out to you
guys. Yes, the journey might have seemed
fun or it might have seemed quick, but
it definitely wasn't quick. It
definitely wasn't fun, but it is
definitely worth it at the end of it
because you show up every single day and
you do something that you genuinely
love. And I will say this, I did not
genuinely love trading at the beginning,
but once I started actually
understanding it and I started
perfecting my craft, I fell in love with
it. And it no longer was work. It was
just showing up to do what I love. Now
it's just becoming my second nature. I
just can't live without it. Like you
can't live without eating or drinking
water or eating food. Same exact thing.
I can't live without looking at the
markets. It's just part of my routine.
It is who I am. I feel weird if I don't
have it involved in my life. And you got
to figure out a skill set where you
connect with it just like that. So it's
not work. So when you're struggling,
when you're failing, when you're losing,
you don't think about it. You don't
think about the monetary value to those
losses. You just see it as part of the
game. You charge it to the game. That's
the message that I want to send across.
And I think what really got me to this
point that I am now, just doing it
because I actually genuinely liked it.
And at this point in my life, I feel
like I've achieved a lot of [__] I
think I've generally done a lot. Like I
look back and I'm like, dude, how the
[__] did you even do all this [__] so
fast? I'm 25 years old now. I've made a
lot of money. I've done a lot of crazy
cool stuff. But the point where I am now
in my life is I want to be the best in
my industry. I want to be the best
possible trader and the only way to do
that is by doing it in my opinion with
the largest sums of money. So right now
I'm currently getting licensed. I'm
getting my series 3 33 and 34 so I can
open up a fund and just manage a bunch
of money. I have so many rich friends
that want to throw me money all the
time. And I'm going to be getting my
license now so I can trade multiple
funds. I'm going to be opening up a
trading floor very soon here in Miami.
We're going to be traveling to Dubai
this weekend actually precisely to just
start kind of dabbling in the market
over there. But bro, I have some nasty
traders in my community that have
learned my strategy and I've scaled it
over time and they're going to be part
of of my fund. My goal is to make
anywhere from five to six% a month for
investors and I'm going to do everything
the right way. I'm going to get
licensed, you know, taking one to two
trades a week. That's kind of where my
my my projection, my plan is going to
and just [__] live it up, honestly.
Like, we want to travel the world, bro.
We're going to travel now. Like, we
traveled a lot 2 years ago when we
started getting money, then we locked in
to get more money, and now we're just
good and we're just going to go travel
pretty much everywhere. give back more.
I can't buy any more supercars. I can't
buy any more cool [__] Like, I've
already bought everything as
materialistic as it gets. But I do want
to go buy cool experiences and cool
moments that buddy to a certain extent
can even buy. You just have to kind of
be there and make it happen. And I think
that's where my next phase and my next
fun is going to be. So, I'm excited. But
if there's one message that I can say to
you guys, uh, you know, just to close
this video out is that it's not too late
to start, just because I started on this
journey when I was 18, fresh out of high
school and I happen to have supportive,
you know, family and I was in a very
good household, doesn't mean that I have
an advantage over you. Doesn't mean that
I have something that you need for you
to get to where I am right now. I know
people in much worse situations that I
am and have been able to get out of that
and be bigger than what I am. So, don't
ever use your current situations as an
excuse to get where you want to be.
You're in that situation for a reason.
You were put there for a reason, and
that's to challenge you to get out of
that actual position that you're in. And
if you weren't strong enough to get out
of there, you would have never been put
that in that position. And maybe you put
yourself in that position, you did some
dumb decisions that got you there. And
that's totally fine. I have done that as
well. But I have made up for it and I
get myself out of those positions. So,
it's never too late to start in whatever
it is that you want to do. But what I
will tell you is that it does take
relentless work and not giving a [__]
about what anybody says and showing up
every single [__] day, even when
things get tough. So with that being
said, see you boys in the next video.
Hit that subscribe button. Let's go to
Dubai.
[music and singing]
>> [music and singing]
>> right now in the city. So face so
I in the city it's okay
[music]
down
[singing] Penny X
>> [music]
>> Away.